THREE IDIOTS IN KENYA
-The squid earlier--
-What's that?
What is that?
-It is sundae?
-Is that bulgogi?
-Bulgogi.
-It's bulgogi.
This dish needs recognition.
A CLASSIC SWEET AND SALTY DISH
BULGOGI
I can drink two bottles with this.
THEY'RE DESPERATELY IN NEED OF FOOD
Let's change the game this time.
The category is animals.
Guess the Animal Quiz.
-I think we need to guess the names.
-Really?
-It's hard.
-I'm not good at this.
GUESS THE ANIMAL QUIZ
Like when we guess people,
-I'll show you animal pictures.
-Oh no.
NAME THE ANIMAL IN THE PICTURE
MONGOOSE
BUFFALO
Shall we start?
If Ji-won guesses correctly,
you will go over to that side.
Let's go.
-This will be easy.
-What was the animal that ran away?
-Gazelle.
-No, it was something bigger.
-Impala?
-That's right.
-What are you whispering about?
-He's a real expert.
-He knows everything.
-He's amazing.
I just like animals.
Why are you suddenly acting humble?
It doesn't suit you.
Hold on.
I saw him show off
and then get humiliated.
EXAMPLES:
LEONARDO DICAPRIO, ABRAHAM CADABRA
Okay, we'll start with Ji-won.
-I'll go slow this time.
-All right.
BULGOGI ROUND
-Three, two, one.
-Pumbaa.
Correct.
-Three, two, one.
-Hyena.
-Correct!
-What a relief.
Three, two, one.
-Fox rabbit.
-Incorrect!
-"Fox rabbit"?
-Did you say fox rabbit?
-It's a fennec fox.
-Isn't that from a cartoon?
-We've never seen it here.
We chose commonly known animals.
-But…
-Not just the animals we see here?
In the Maasai Mara.
Look at them complaining too.
"That's not fair."
FEELING WRONGED
-If only you had said "fox."
-Isn't it a fennec fox?
Where did the fox rabbit come from?
It's a fox that resembles a rabbit.
I was wrong.
Hey, why don't we try this?
There are four questions left.
You get to eat if Ji-won gets them all.
-Let's do it.
-Yes.
-Sure, I can do it.
-I'm counting on you.
Okay, I'll get them all.
I should know
since I've seen so many animals.
-He's a renowned animal expert.
-Okay.
He has done research on the Maasai Mara
for 24 years.
-He published a book recently.
-Yes.
Never Speak of the Things
You Saw in the Maasai Mara.
That's the book…
What's the point
of publishing a book then?
-It's Dr. Eun's dark side.
-That's hilarious.
-I've made many darkmentaries.
-Yes, he did.
They are dark documentaries.
-You can see his…
-Dark side?
-That's right.
-Definitely.
Never Speak of the Things
You Saw in the Maasai Mara
is a two-page book.
He can't write that well.
FAITHFUL TO THE TITLE
-Let's start.
-Let's do this.
-I can do this.
-This is Ji-won's challenge.
-Ji-won, relax.
-All right.
-We won't say anything.
-It's okay to get it wrong.
Hey, take a shot!
-Stop it.
-No way.
-I can't think clearly.
-Got it.
I get confused.
Let's go.
BULGOGI ROUND
-Three, two, one.
-Water strider.
Correct.
PASSED AN UNEXPECTED QUESTION
-That was unexpected.
-How did he get that?
Three, two, one.
The… That…
Red panda.
-Correct.
-Red panda?
-Three, two, one.
-That… ant…
-Anteater.
-Correct.
-What is that?
-This is insane.
-Dr. Eun.
-Wait, there's only one left.
-I can't believe this.
-He's awesome.
This is impressive.
Let's jump right into the last question.
They might give out a hard one.
Three, two, one.
That's a…
-Sloth!
-Correct.
-Wasn't it a gorilla?
-I thought it was King Kong.
-Am I right?
-Is he?
Correct!
-I got them all right.
-Dr. Eun.
Correct!
RESPECT
-Do I qualify as an expert?
-You surely do.
How did you recognize the sloth?
-I didn't know any of the others.
-Even the anteater.
-It's incredible.
-He sure is Dr. Dark Eun.
-Why don't you have a shot to celebrate?
-Me?
-Come here.
-Let's all make a toast.
-Of course.
-Sure.
For bulgogi.
Cheers to the darkmentary professor.
-Cheers.
-You were great.
-To the darkmentary professor.
WON THE BULGOGI
-He did great.
-That was awesome.
Ji-won, you're something else.
The pictures were hard to see.
I couldn't make out the water strider.
BULGOGI TIME
-I watch lots of animal videos.
-I can tell.
Hey, there are chilis inside.
It's so good.
MVP JI-WON TAKES A BITE
IT'S DELICIOUS
KYUHYUN EATS IT WITH RICE
I like that it's spicy.
AFTER DEVOURING THE BULGOGI
It looks like stew.
It's kimchi stew.
GOOD TIMING FOR STEW
-Let's eat this.
-Shouldn't you win this?
PERFECT FOR WARMING YOUR BELLY AND SOUL
KIMCHI STEW FILLED WITH MEAT
CHUCKLES
Honestly, I'm loving this right now.
I feel happy for some reason.
I'm just happy, even if I'm wrong.
THEY MUST BE DRUNK
Don't you just love this?
-Look at the sunset.
-You can catch a glimpse of the sunset.
THE TWILIGHT BRINGS THE MOOD
Well, I would appreciate it
if you ended the game
before the hippos come out.
Dr. Eun, when are hippos active?
-Hippos are active at night.
-After the sun sets…
-They come out to catch prey.
-Right.
-I thought they were herbivores.
-They are.
They won't eat us,
but they can kill us if we annoy them.
-Then shouldn't we report it?
-We should.
-We should be careful first.
-I see.
-Since we're in their territory?
-That's right.
-But they come up often.
-They do.
Because the sun is setting.
We'll get a bit drunk later,
and if the hippos come out…
Su-geun will spot them and say,
"Hey, Pumbaa."
He'll approach them and say,
"Pumbaa is so cute!"
-He will crawl toward the hippo.
-Excuse me.
-It's not dangerous if it's unintentional.
-Why?
They'd be surprised too.
"I've never seen a human
-come up to me."
-You're the first.
The hippo might even back off.
Did they come out?
They're coming!
They're on the way!
They're making their way across the river.
QUICKLY RESUMING THE GAME
-Let's play your all-time favorite game.
-What can it be?
Bestsellers.
-What? Bestsellers?
-Let's try that.
-They're trying to make us lose.
-Right.
Hold on, let's…
STRATEGIZING
-Namiye--
-Keep it down.
-"Namiye."
-It's Namiya, not Namiye.
Miracles of the Namiya General Store.
-The 100-Year-Old Man…
-What?
The 100-year-old man did what?
The 100-year-old man is still alive.
INADVERTENTLY TURNING IT
INTO A HEALTH BOOK
-Who Climbed Out the Window…
-We'll lose this round.
Okay, let's do this. Come on.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Three, two, one.
-Took a punch.
Took a punch.
Guess the bestsellers.
KIMCHI STEW ROUND
Please be gentle with us.
Let's go.
Rich Dad?
Poor Mom.
-Incorrect!
-Oh no!
Poor Mom.
-Incorrect!
-Oh no!
I should've guessed this one.
This is the most famous book on economics.
What's the answer?
How about, "Rich dad is not my dad"?
"Rich dad is not my dad."
Can't this be the title?
KIMCHI STEW IS OUT
The last dish…
-Is it pork belly?
-Really?
…is a grilled pork belly set menu.
THE ULTIMATE KOREAN COMFORT FOOD
PORK BELLY
Since you three are playing as a team…
-We can't win.
-It's not easy, right?
You'll be playing solo for the last round.
-What's that?
-The Manager's Challenge.
You'll be treating everyone.
If you win on your own,
everyone gets to eat together.
PLAYER
TEAM LEADER LEE SU-GEUN
If Mr. Lee succeeds,
you can have all the pork belly you want.
If he fails, dinner will end immediately.
What's the game?
It's what you do best.
Let's play charades.
With who?
He will act out the words,
and you two will guess.
If you guess all ten correctly, you win.
-What?
-All of them?
-Try to guess ten in three minutes.
-We can do this.
Let's go. We've got this.
CHARADES PLAYED BY SU-GEUN
-Should I reveal the category?
-Move this away.
It's food franchises.
Wow, this is too difficult.
-You take the lead.
-Let's do this.
Food franchises include coffee, food…
-If it's food, I'll do this.
-Okay.
-If it's coffee, I'll pretend to drink.
-Yes.
-This is for ice cream.
-Got it.
-Are you ready?
-These bugs.
-There are bugs, but--
-It's okay.
Don't think they're bugs.
Let's hurry.
Anck-Su-Namun.
STAYING POSITIVE IN DIFFICULT TIMES
Let's begin.
Ready.
They will give us time.
Set, go.
THE GAME STARTS
FIRST CATEGORY IS PIZZA
DOMINO'S PIZZA
IT'S FOOD
IT'S ROUND
AND YOU SLICE IT
Mr. Pizza.
Pizza Hut.
-Pizza Etang.
-Domino's Pizza.
-Correct.
OFF TO A GOOD START
NEW CATEGORY, BURGERS
MOM'S TOUCH
TOUCH
-What is it? Show us first.
-Is it food or drink?
It's food.
Touch.
-Mom's Touch.
-Correct.
GUESSED 2 CORRECTLY IN A FLASH
BONJUK
HEARTY NOURISHING FOOD
-It's food.
You eat it in a bowl. You cool it down.
It's hot.
-It's soup.
-Gukbap?
Is it soup?
-Soup?
TWO WORDS
-Two words? Gukbap?
Devour a bowl.
HEARTY MEAL
NEW STRATEGY
Tired? You're sleeping.
STOMACHACHE
-You're sick.
FEELING SYMPATHY FOR HIM
-You eat this when you're sick?
-You're sick…
-Bonjuk.
-Correct.
FINALLY
They're good at this.
GIMBAP HEAVEN
ROLL
-You roll it.
-Gimbap!
-Gimbap Heaven.
-Heaven!
HOLY SUCCESS
Way to go!
NENE CHICKEN
CATEGORY IS LATE-NIGHT SNACK
Hello.
Chicken.
-Chicken.
-Cheogajip.
It's a chicken brand.
Birdbrain?
It's saying hello. Hello chicken?
FOUR WORDS
Puradak Chicken.
EXCEPTIONALLY POSITIVE CHICKEN
-Cock-a-doodle.
-NeNe Chicken.
Correct! He's on a roll.
ISAAC TOAST
CATEGORY IS TOAST
GRAIN
You plant it.
-Are you eating a lettuce wrap?
-Ssambap?
-Do you eat it from the ground?
-Sprout?
2 WORDS
Two words?
NEW STRATEGY
POP
Oh, toast. Isaac Toast.
-Correct.
-I had no clue.
KKANBU CHICKEN
WE'RE KKANBU
You and me.
-A promise?
-We're making a promise.
Promise Chicken?
Whisper.
Damn it.
FRUSTRATED
You and me.
-How many words?
-You and me.
-Ttakji.
-Ttakji?
Ttakji Chicken.
Kkanbu Chicken!
Correct.
PENT-UP ANGER
I don't know Kkanbu Chicken.
SULBING
MOVING ON TO DESSERT
EXPLAINS THE ICE SHAVING MACHINE FIRST
It's ice cream.
Two syllables? Brain freeze?
It's cold. Bingsu?
THAT'S PART OF THIS NAME
-Sulbing.
-Correct.
Oh my.
JI-WON GUESSES CORRECTLY
BEFORE SU-GEUN GETS UPSET
MYUNGRANG HOTDOG
NATIONAL FAVORITE SNACK
It's a rice cake.
Churros.
Cotton candy. Lollipop?
He's drizzling something on it.
Ketchup.
Hotdog!
IN A CHEERFUL WAY
Exercise…
-Hotdog?
-Healthy dog?
-Myungrang Hotdog.
-Correct.
FINALLY GOT HIS CHEERFULNESS
SUBWAY
It's the last one.
-Let's get this one.
-What's that?
The freeway.
THAT'S RIGHT
LOOK AT THIS!
California rolls.
What is it? The boat.
Subway.
-That's right!
-Really?
-Correct!
-We got it.
I meant to say freeway in English.
You should've said that in English.
Isn't high road…
-Is it highway?
-Yes.
Subway's the same thing.
It doesn't matter.
We got it right.
We just understood you.
-Subway--
-How did you get it right?
Because the words are similar.
I figured it was something like that.
GOT LUCKY
Can you do NeNe Chicken again?
NE
NENE CHICKEN
AN ENCORE-DESERVING DESCRIPTION
That was an encore for NeNe Chicken.
Congratulations.
Enjoy your meal.
-We did it.
-Let's eat.
TIME TO FEAST
Enjoy, everyone.
-Thank you.
-Hold on.
Should I eat first?
-You eat first.
-You can eat first. I'll grill the meat.
It's raining. Bring the umbrella.
This is…
From both angles.
AMAZED
-This is happiness.
-Exactly.
This is true happiness.
-Let's toast.
-Sure.
-Cheers.
SNEEZES
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
FEELS HEARTWARMING WITH GOOD FOOD
I'll make a wrap.
-We should eat a wrap.
-Of course.
SU-GEUN MAKES A LETTUCE WRAP
I should add two pieces of meat.
Add grilled kimchi on top.
-Shouldn't you add rice too?
-That's a must.
OPENS WIDE
It's too big for my mouth.
I want to wrap it in pickled radish.
OPENS WIDER
JI-WON MAKES A PICKLED RADISH WRAP
Director Eun.
NOM
It's so good.
-It's better than any restaurant.
-Definitely.
SU-GEUN'S IMPRESSIVE GRILLING
Let's make fried rice.
TIME FOR KOREAN DESSERT
-Add kimchi.
-Okay.
WHAT'S HIS RECIPE?
1. CUT THE MEAT INTO PIECES
2. CHOP IT UP MORE
You have to film him making fried rice.
-Can you lower the heat?
-Sure.
Wow, Su-geun.
His scissors don't touch the frying pan.
3. STIR-FRY WITH RICE AND KIMCHI
TODAY'S CHEF HAS LOTS OF EXPERIENCE
Gochujang.
4. GOCHUJANG AND SSAMJANG
AS KEY INGREDIENTS
-Did you run a barbecue place?
-Yes, I did everything.
HE'S EVEN HUMBLE
I want to be your son.
I would give you a big allowance.
Sprinkle a bit of pepper, please.
KOREAN DESSERT IS READY
-This is definitely tasty.
-Absolutely.
CHEF TAKES A BITE FIRST
Thank you.
It's so good.
It's yummy.
KYUHYUN TAKES A BITE
Kyuhyun, it's great.
MOVED
Are we still missing two of the Big Five?
-The rhino and the leopard?
-And the lion.
Oh, we haven't seen three yet.
Let me tell you tomorrow's schedule.
-Sure.
-Okay
-You did a game drive today.
-Yes.
We'll be in the sky
to see the wildlife tomorrow.
-Really? How?
-Is that true?
There's a hot-air balloon here.
NO WAY!
-I saw it.
-That's on my bucket list.
We won't be riding it just anytime.
It's great during the sunrise…
Early in the morning?
-You'll watch the safari as the sun rises.
-Wow, I think I'm going to cry.
HOT-AIR BALLOON SNEAK PEEK
After the hot-air balloon ride,
we'll leave the eco-friendly lodge
and go to a luxury lodge.
Wow, thank you.
We're making great memories, right?
WRAPPING UP THE DAY
WITH HEARTY KOREAN FOOD
4:20 A.M. BEFORE THE CRACK OF DAWN
We need to wake up.
STIR
UP EARLY FOR THE SAFARI SUNRISE
HALF ASLEEP
-Good morning.
Morning.
EVEN SLEEPYHEAD JI-WON WOKE UP
Where's the coffee?
POURS
POURING COFFEE INTO THEIR OWN TUMBLERS
-Oh, my hand.
-Be careful.
Did I spill?
Oh, I didn't spill.
This is just heating up.
The thermos is getting hot.
It's too thin. It's not a thermos.
A BOTTLE DISGUISED AS THERMOS
It's an ordinary bottle.
Do you think I'm lying?
TRY IT YOURSELF
He's telling the truth. It's hot.
I thought I had spilled it on my hand
while pouring it.
WELL, AT LEAST HE MUST BE FULLY AWAKE NOW
-This is no joke.
-Why is it so hot?
BURN HAZARD
TO THE YOUNGER IDIOT WHO ARRIVED LATE
I prepared this iced chocolate for you.
-For me?
-Yes.
Oh, my hands! Gosh, it's hot!
It's so hot!
IT WAS HOT ICED CHOCOLATE
I was shocked.
I thought I spilled coffee on my hand.
-Why does it get so hot?
-It really does.
Let's head out.
LEAVING THEIR FIRST LODGE IN THE SAFARI
TO RIDE THE HOT-AIR BALLOON
It might take a bit over an hour,
so get a good rest before we arrive.
WE WERE TOLD TO GET SOME REST
I don't think I can get a good rest.
SWAYS
-I won't be able to rest properly.
-Kyuhyun, rest up.
FLUTTERING LIKE A PAPER DOLL
-You didn't have enough sleep.
-That's right.
RIDING ON THE BUMPY OFF-ROAD TRAIL
-There are hyenas in front of us.
-Look at the hyenas.
Straight ahead.
I see their eyes.
-Wow, hyenas.
-Look at their eyes.
EXCITED BY THE UNEXPECTED ENCOUNTER
-Spotted hyenas.
-They don't run away.
SPOTTED HYENA
NOCTURNAL ANIMALS OF KENYA
There are a few sitting down.
EXUDING A UNIQUE ALLURE
They're real hyenas.
HYENAS AT DAWN
This is unbelievable.
We're in the middle of the time
when animals are active.
RIDING AT DAWN IN THE WILD
IT'S DAYBREAK BEFORE YOU KNOW IT
THE THREE IDIOTS FELL ASLEEP
Wait, it's a giraffe.
It's a giraffe.
-What?
-A giraffe.
-Look, there's a giraffe!
-Where?
TALL FIGURES ARE FAINTLY VISIBLE
On your right.
-They're on both sides.
-There it is.
-On my left.
-Here it is.
AMAZED
GIRAFFES THEY'VE BEEN WAITING FOR
They're walking around at this hour?
Wow, it's a herd of giraffes.
A HERD OF GIRAFFES ON THE MOVE
JI-WON AND KYUHYUN ARE FASCINATED BY THEM
BLINKS
TRYING HARD TO STAY AWAKE
-There's a big one.
-It's huge.
MAASAI GIRAFFE
INHABITS KENYA AND TANZANIA
The sun is setting on the left.
THE SUN IS RISING, NOT SETTING
THEIR SILHOUETTES AT DAWN
LOOK LIKE A PAINTING
It looks abundant here
since there is water.
I guess they're here to drink water.
AFTER FINALLY ENCOUNTERING GIRAFFES
Look ahead.
The sun is rising.
FASCINATED
I've never seen a sun glow like this.
SUNLIGHT GRADUALLY PAINTS THE SKY
ABOVE THE HORIZON
-The hot-air balloons are over there.
-They're on my right.
APPROACHING THE MASSIVE HOT-AIR BALLOONS
They're amazing.
This is on a whole different level.
I'm excited.
We have arrived.
Jambo.
Wow, they're firing it up.
THE HOT-AIR BALLOON IS BEING INFLATED
-Do we have to lie down?
-No, we have to stand up.
BICKERING ONCE AGAIN
-We have to lie down like I said.
-Okay.
-What?
-We must lie down.
Oh, this is a bit different.
THE THREE IDIOTS BOARD THE HOT-AIR BALLOON
This is incredible.
Do you want me to hold a camera?
SU-GEUN'S CAMERA
How do you feel?
Honestly, I'm scared.
-Isn't this your first time?
-Yes, actually, this is…
NERVOUS
Wow, it's moving.
STARTING TO INFLATE THE HOT-AIR BALLOON
THE EXCITED THREE IDIOTS ARE ALL SET
It's going up.
ALL READY FOR TAKEOFF
It feels strange.
That pilot is awesome.
He looks like a fire bender.
WITH HIS FLAMETHROWER SKILLS
AS THE FIRE BENDER
I think we're in the air.
We're rising.
THE HOT-AIR BALLOON GRADUALLY RISES
-We're up in the air.
-Yes, we are.
He told us to stand up.
ASTONISHED
It's insane!
This seat is amazing.
AMAZED
This is incredible. I can't believe it.
This is unbelievable.
THE HIGHLIGHT OF MAASAI MARA,
HOT-AIR BALLOONS
It's amazing how we are in the air.
It feels like a dream.
This is unreal.
-I'm speechless.
-The sun is rising on this side.
-Is it really?
-The sun is rising on the left.
STUNNED
BREATHTAKING EXPERIENCE WITH A SUNRISE
There are so many hot-air balloons around.
This is when they usually take off.
MOST POPULAR AT SUNRISE
I'm not anyone special,
but I highly suggest this for a honeymoon.
STUNNED
The ride is very comfortable.
It feels like a waterbed or some sort of…
It feels soft. The ride is smooth.
It's such a stable ride.
TENSION FADES AWAY WITH A STABLE RIDE
Take a look below.
Are those gazelles?
A HERD OF GAZELLES
Look over there.
They're hopping around.
They are so cute.
-The hyenas are…
-They're following gazelles.
HYENAS FOLLOWING GAZELLES
They're running away from the hyenas.
The hyenas are going after an impala…
I mean, a gazelle for a meal.
-It would be great to see a lion.
-I really hope so.
AS THE IDIOTS WISH FOR A LION
-Are those birds?
-They are.
We are flying above the birds.
THEY GET TO SEE THE TOP OF THE HEADS
OF THE FLYING EGRETS
-Where are the buffalo?
-Buffalo?
There are so many of them.
A HERD OF BUFFALO
-Look at the elephants near the trees.
-Wow, I see them.
THEY ENCOUNTER ELEPHANTS AGAIN
It's running.
They're having a fight.
Look at them use horns.
They're going at it with their horns.
Why start the day off fighting?
You shouldn't be fighting.
EVEN TRIES TO STOP THE TOPI FROM FIGHTING
It seems like there aren't
as many lions today.
NOT A SINGLE STRAND OF MANE IS SEEN
They must be sleeping.
Yes, I…
You shouldn't sing.
I do
I made this song.
COPYRIGHT-FREE MADE-UP SONG
I wish I could fly up into the air
Stop it.
I have a dream
AS HE TRIES TO WOO THE LION
-There are lions near the buffalo.
-Where?
-In front of the buffalo herd?
Where are the buffalo?
UNABLE TO LOCATE THE BUFFALO
LET'S GET A LITTLE CLOSER
LOOKING CLOSELY
-I see the lions.
-Where?
Do you see the black line of buffalo?
Find the black line.
They're just below it.
-Is it in front of the car?
-Yes.
-The lion is in front of the car.
-It is.
-He said the lions are by the car.
-Near the car.
A SMALL GROUP PASSING BY THE CAR
-I thought they moved solo.
-I see five or six of them.
-There are more than ten.
-Look at all of them.
A LARGER GROUP FOLLOWS THEM
Lions travel in groups known as a pride.
Four of them are walking by.
LION PRIDE PASSING BY
I see four or five of them moving across.
AFRICAN LION
KING OF THE JUNGLE
REPRESENTATIVE CARNIVORES OF AFRICA
THEY LIVE IN PRIDES OF 20 LIONS
-Right there.
-The wind is taking us to the lions!
-We are lucky.
-We are going toward the lions.
-They might go hunting.
-It looks like they are about to.
The lions are about to start their hunt.
The lioness is leading the group
moving toward that way to hunt.
With the wind blowing toward the buffalo,
the lions wait for it to shift
to hide their scent.
The buffalo will run away
if they catch it.
They lie low
and wait until the wind shifts.
When do you think they'll start hunting?
I think it might take some time.
Like 20… Maybe in ten minutes?
-We hoped to see them hunt.
-Can we stay for ten minutes?
DESPERATE
ONLY IF THE WIND STOPS
LET'S GIVE UP
SINCE WE CAN'T DRIFT IN THE AIR
We still got to see the lions.
GOT TO SEE THE LIONS ON THE LAST TOUR
The vibe they show is really something.
-It sure is different.
-They look laid back.
They stroll leisurely along the road.
There's nothing that can stop them.
-They don't want to hurt their feet.
-Yes, the road is nicely made.
And the pathway has been made.
Strolling on the road.
If I had to be born again,
I would choose to be a lion.
MY DREAM FOR MY NEXT LIFE
I get why they're kings of the jungle.
If born a gazelle,
you'd have to run all day.
They must always be cautious,
even when eating.
How about Pumbaa?
Pumbaa would be okay,
but I'm worried about my elbows.
I CHOOSE LION TO PROTECT MYSELF
-They eat leaning on their elbows.
-They're my favorites.
BIG 5 LOG
LION SIGHTING SUCCESSFUL
MOVING ALONG AFTER LION SIGHTSEEING
We didn't get to see the rhinos.
I heard it's really hard to spot them.
-Did we see them during the site visit?
-We did.
-Did you not film during site visits?
Just give us some reaction by saying,
"Look at the rhinos."
Look, there are rhinos!
Stop lying.
-We can edit this line into that footage.
-Is that what it is? I almost fell for it.
THE REMAINING BIG 5 MISSED BY THE IDIOTS
THESE ARE RHINOS
TO BE EXACT, THE BLACK RHINOS
BLACK RHINO
RARE AND HARD TO SPOT
EATS LEAVES
HAS TRIANGULAR MOUTH
THIS ONE IS A WHITE RHINO
WHITE RHINOCEROS
LIVES IN NORTH-CENTRAL REGION OF KENYA
BIGGEST IN SIZE
NEXT IS THE LEOPARD
AFRICAN LEOPARD
KNOWN FOR THEIR ROSETTE PATTERN
INHABITS BUSHES AND TREES
THE HARDEST TO SPOT AMONG THE BIG 5
BIG 5 LOG
SIGHTSEEING COMPLETE, IN A WAY
PHOTO TIME AFTER SEEING THE BIG 5
I can't open my eyes.
TRULY A BRIGHT AND UNFORGETTABLE MEMORY
RUMMAGES
-Coffee, anyone?
-You have all sorts of things.
ENJOYING HOT COFFEE AFTER THE PHOTO TIME
SELF-SERVED MEAL AT DIFFERENT ALTITUDES
GETTING CLOSER TO THE GROUND
-Please get ready for landing.
-Seat belt, please.
We're close to the ground. That was fast.
SUCCESSFUL LANDING
You are the best driver.
Let's all clap. Everybody clap.
WE MADE IT
Let's hear you sing.
AFTER THE HOT-AIR BALLOON TOUR
PICNIC TIME BEFORE HEADING TO THE LODGE
ENJOYING THEIR LEISURE TIME
Can eggs be this delicious?
Are we really enjoying our picnic here?
ELEPHANT FAMILY DINING ON THE SIDE
Everything is great, even the wind.
A PERFECT ACACIA TREE AHEAD
How was the hot-air balloon ride?
It was the best.
The safari definitely
looked different from above.
On most hot-air balloon rides,
you mostly look at scenery,
but we saw animals as well.
-The impression is still strong.
-Really.
-It's something…
-It's something you need to experience.
Seriously…
Can we get eaten out of nowhere?
If you fall asleep, you might die.
If I have to sleep here,
I'm going to soak my hair in orange juice.
It lets them devour my head first.
That would be less painful.
Isn't that right?
Ants might attack you first.
Anything is fine.
Since the weather is nice
and we're having a picnic,
we should try something fun.
Why don't we have a poetry contest
based on our experiences in Africa?
SAFARI WRITING CONTEST
WRITE A POEM INSPIRED BY AFRICA
REQUEST AN EVALUATION FROM CHATGPT
RANKINGS BASED ON CRITERIA CHOSEN BY AI
What does the winner get?
The winner will receive
the Golden Coffee Beans left by Ji-won.
THE 1ST PLACE PRIZE
THE 2 GOLDEN COFFEE BEANS
THE MAFIA LEFT BEHIND
That sound good.
Don't we all have a sense of sensitivity?
The title is set as "Africa."
TITLE: AFRICA
Please be creative.
Dr. Eun has already started writing.
WRITING WITHOUT HESITATION
You're really quick.
You shouldn't be cheating.
I'm sorry,
but that doesn't help me at all.
NO DESIRE TO CHEAT ON HIS WRITING
Don't look at mine!
AS THE OLDER IDIOTS ARE BICKERING
THE LONELY POET CHO APPEARS
Kyuhyun, you are a singer.
Do it with all your heart.
AFRICA
SOAKING IN THE PEAK OF EMOTIONS
OLDEST IDIOT IS FULLY COMMITTED
AFRICA
BY LEE SU-GEUN
TRYING HIS BEST WITHOUT PLAGIARIZING
IDIOTS FULLY FOCUSED IN THEIR WRITING
I'm done.
SUBMISSION COMPLETE
Were you in serious mode, Su-geun?
I wanted to do something with Pumbaa, but…
I prefer sincerity over humor for this.
Yes, since you mentioned that earlier.
Who would like to read first?
-I'll go first since mine is the shortest.
-Okay, let's give it up for him.
-I wrote it so we can all be part of it.
-Okay.
Please say the first letters together.
-You wrote an acrostic poem.
-Acrostic?
Title, Africa. Written by Eun Ji-won.
-A.
"A beautiful scenery."
-F.
"Freely roaming animals across the field."
-Ri.
"Respect, Africa."
Ah.
-It's "ca." Why did you say "ah"?
-Ca…
Why do you spoil the fun?
-Just like how you express that sound.
-Right.
"Captivating moments fill the air."
Oh, okay.
-That was great.
-I thought of this as well.
Could you share your inspiration?
The poem sincerely expresses
my feelings about Africa.
My genuine feelings.
UNNATURAL TONE
I understand.
-Su-geun, please go ahead and read yours.
-Okay.
SU-GEUN'S TURN
Africa.
Written by Lee Su-geun.
"Warm sun, cool breeze, and their smiles,
a soothing pause for the traveler.
The first flutter
of nature's wonder in 50 years.
Nature's roar stirs my passion
and brings back memories of my youth.
Youth, it's Africa."
STRUGGLES WITH SERIOUS MOMENTS
-He's just feeling embarrassed.
-I'm sorry.
At last, Kyuhyun's turn.
He writes lyrics, so he'd be good.
-I only compose.
-Oh, you don't write.
Africa.
Written by Kyuhyun.
Put some feeling into it, please.
He should've written as Ostrich Cho.
AFRICA
BY OSTRICH CHO
-"That's right."
-"That's right"?
That's great.
"Everyone wants to be in the spotlight.
The king of the jungle, lion.
A hippo that can take down a lion.
A cheetah with speed.
A giant elephant.
But I have no desire for competition.
I prefer to humbly kneel down
and feed on the grass."
-It's Pumbaa.
-It is.
"That's right.
-I am Pumbaa."
-That idiot.
I knew it.
-"I am Pumbaa."
-That idiot.
I knew it.
"A Pumbaa with dreams."
"A Pumbaa with dreams"?
-The story is…
-Why? What's wrong?
HEARTBROKEN PUMBAA CHO
As it got closer to the end,
I had a feeling Pumbaa would be mentioned.
Everyone sensed
that you were going to mention Pumbaa.
A BUILD-UP LEADING TO PUMBAA
Shouldn't the title be "Pumbaa"?
EVALUATION COMPLETE
-The three poems are not for us to judge.
-Okay.
We'll ask ChatGPT
to evaluate for us again.
-Should I read them to you?
-Yes.
THE IDIOTS' POEMS WERE SENT TO CHATGPT
"Yes, Your Highness."
A TRAINED SKILL
"All three poems impressively
explored Africa in their own way.
I will rank and rate
each poem based on four criteria.
The criteria are creativity,
delivery of the theme,
emotional impact, and literary quality."
-There is no category regarding humor.
-Right.
I might score high in emotional impact.
I went more with humor.
FULL OF CONCERNS
FIRST CONTESTANT
EUN JI-WON
For our first contestant, Ji-won.
"A rhythmic acrostic focused on wordplay
and onomatopoeic expressions."
-That's spot on.
-It recognized it.
LEFT A POSITIVE IMPRESSION
"In terms of creativity,
the use of slang expressions
like 'respect' stands out,
and 'Ca' adds a unique touch.
In terms of emotional impact,
it conveys excitement
but lacks depth in emotional layers.
In terms of literary quality,
it has rhythm
but feels like a humorous cliché."
Did it say cliché?
It said cliché.
Why is it cliché?
AI CHALLENGED HIS PRIDE
What nonsense is this?
It comes across like clichés from ads.
I see.
"Overall, a witty and unforgettable poem,
much like a great advertising slogan.
I rate it 3 out of 5 stars."
It keeps rating mine three stars.
AI FOUND NO STRONG POINTS IN HIS POEM
Did you end up writing his name?
QUESTIONABLE FAIRNESS IN CONSISTENCY
It's not very giving of you.
For our second contestant, Kyuhyun.
"A self-exploratory poem
through animal metaphors."
Wow, it read my mind.
-It knows you well.
-Yes.
A TRUE FRIEND FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD
It understands him so well.
"For creativity,
impersonating an animal
to contrast social desires feels new."
TOUCHED
It noticed.
"For emotional impact,
the line 'I am Pumbaa'
blends humor and philosophy."
IMPRESSED
-It captured all the meanings?
-How did it know?
INTERPRETATION BEATS THE DREAM
"I didn't even know."
"Overall, it's a humorous
and philosophical confession from Pumbaa."
"Confession from Pumbaa."
The rating is surprisingly good.
"I rate it 4.3 out of 5 stars."
SURPRISED
A FRIEND'S GENEROUS TAKE
-"Confession from Pumbaa"?
-He was basically Pumbaa.
-I was immersed in the moment.
Why don't you embrace your inner Pumbaa?
-You should stay like that.
-Yes.
PUMBAA CHO THRILLED WITH THE HIGH SCORE
Our last contestant, Su-geun.
"A narrative poem
that reflects on life and youth
-through the grandeur of nature."
-That's right.
"As for emotional impact,
emotions are conveyed in a deep,
resonant voice that is warm and sincere."
-Did it hear my voice?
-Did it?
"As for literary quality,
it is a prose poem
balancing metaphor and sensory details."
-Good interpretation.
-What's a prose poem?
-I've never heard of it.
-"Final note.
A poet in the later chapters of life…"
It was written before death.
"A poet in life's later chapter
finds youth in nature.
I rate it 4.5 out of 5 stars."
Su-geun wins!
POET LEE DEBUTS
-He won.
-I won again.
TAKES HOME TWO TITLES
THE CHAMPION CELEBRATES WITH JOY
-Su-geun…
-I should've included "hakuna matata."
CONSECUTIVELY IN LAST PLACE
As for Su-geun,
we'll present you with the gold beans
shortly after check-in.
Great work, everyone.
Thank you.
MOVING TO THE SECOND LODGE
-This is our final lodge.
-Okay.
Since this is your last lodge,
we have prepared a luxurious one.
We're heading into the forest.
DEEP WITHIN THE FOREST
-What is that?
-What's that sound?
A NOISE COMING FROM FAR AWAY
They made them do that.
I thought we weren't allowed music.
THE SCENE BEFORE THREE IDIOTS IS…
A SPECIAL WELCOMING CEREMONY AT THIS LODGE
Everything is going to be all right
WITH ALL THE WARM WELCOMING
IDIOTS GET OFF ONE BY ONE
THE ONGOING HEARTFELT WELCOME
FILLS THEM WITH EXCITEMENT
LET'S JOIN THEM
SOUNDS GREAT
OLDER IDIOTS WITH GREAT TEAM WORK
THE SINGER IDIOT KEEPS THE BEAT
WITH A WATER BOTTLE
-Hakuna matata
HARMONIZED ENDING
WELCOME
-Hakuna matata!
-Hakuna matata.
A SUDDEN SELF-INTRODUCTION
-Lel.
-Yialel.
-Sharon!
-Sharon.
SELF-INTRODUCTION CONTINUES
-Mike.
WITH ONE VOICE
AS THE SOUND FADES
ALL STAFF INTRODUCTIONS COMPLETE
NICE TO MEET YOU ALL
-Jambo.
JAMBO, IDIOTS
Okay, thank you.
ENTERING THE LODGE
EVEN THE WELCOME IS SPECIAL
SECOND LODGE IN MAASAI MARA
&BEYOND KICHWA TEMBO
POOL WITH A SAFARI VIEW
BEHIND THAT
CHEF PREPARES DISHES
IN A LUXURIOUS DINING SPACE
FEATURING A RELAXING LOUNGE BAR
A HARMONIOUS BLEND OF NATURE AND LUXURY
A LUXURY LODGE TO CROWN THE FINAL NIGHT
-Is that a welcome tea?
-It is a welcome tea.
ASTOUNDED
-This place exudes luxury.
-Look at the building.
-It really is another level.
-It is.
A VISIBLY UPSCALE APPEARANCE
REFRESHING WELCOME TEA
PREPARED FOR THE IDIOTS
There is Pumbaa again.
-Where?
-Over there.
They're everywhere.
A PAIR OF PUMBAA BATHING IN THE SUN
They're relaxing in style.
First of all,
thank you for joining us at the resort.
Thank you for all your work.
The game we will play now is…
-Is this to pick our rooms?
-Yes, it is.
I've been waiting for this game.
ROOM CHOOSING GAME
1ST PLACE: PRIVATE ROOM WITH A SAFARI VIEW
A BIG BED TO USE ALONE
THE REST GET A TWIN ROOM
WITH A FOREST VIEW
SLEEPING SIDE BY SIDE
Having the room by yourself
may not be the best option.
IDIOT WITH SEPARATION ANXIETY
He feels lonely.
I actually feel the same.
A SHY CONFESSION OF LONELINESS
The game we will be doing…
Do you remember the song at the entrance?
-Yes, hakuna matata.
-Hakuna matata
After the song…
-The employees introduced themselves.
-Yes, they did.
GETTING A BAD FEELING
The game is to find "Mike."
NICE TO SEE YOU, MIKE
AFTER THE WELCOME CEREMONY
A SUSPICIOUS BUT SINCERE INTRODUCTION
"MIKE?"
IF YOU FIND MIKE
"NICE TO SEE YOU"
WILL BE THE ANSWER
AND WILL BE GIVEN THE INVITATION
TO THE SAFARI VIEW ROOM
-I'm Mike.
-Mike.
DO THE IDIOTS REMEMBER?
I know the answer.
Just take the room. I have no idea.
We prepared some traits, just in case.
-Should we just start?
-No, tell us.
APPEARANCE AND ATTIRE
The first trait is that
Mike is a person with a smile.
MIKE'S TRAITS
1. A SMILEY FACE
Everyone here is.
ALL SMILES
Everyone was smiling.
His head shape is quite beautiful,
and he's in a dress shirt and pants.
MIKE?
-Can he be avoiding us?
-No, he'll be working in his position.
THERE ARE MANY FIELDS OF WORK
IN THIS LODGE
RECEPTION AREA
YARD
SOUVENIR SHOP
RESTAURANT
BAR
SWIMMING POOL
OUT OF ALL THESE PLACES
WHERE IS MIKE?
You can begin.
THE GAME STARTS
He won't be anywhere close to here.
Smiley face, a dress shirt, and pants…
ARRIVES AT THE BAR WITH HINTS
A SMILEY FACE
BEAUTIFULLY SHAPED HEAD
A DRESS SHIRT AND PANTS
HE DISCOVERED THE IDEAL CANDIDATE
I'm sorry.
EXCHANGED INTRODUCTIONS
BUT IT'S NOT MIKE
SECOND ATTEMPT AT THE BARTENDER
SENSE OF ANTICIPATION
WITH SMILES ON HIS FACE
I'm sorry.
NOT MIKE
LEAVING WITHOUT MUCH INFORMATION
What is this?
Is it a baby Pumbaa?
It's a baby Pumbaa! Oh, dear me!
SORRY, I'M HYRAX
HYRAX
CLOSE GENETIC RELATIVE OF THE ELEPHANT
STICKY PADS ON THEIR FEET
It's cute.
COMPLETELY FOCUSED ON THE HYRAX
He's in a dress shirt.
MEANWHILE, KYUHYUN
He is in a dress shirt and pants.
SEARCHING FOR PEOPLE IN DRESS SHIRTS
RED, WHITE, BEIGE…
THERE ARE JUST SO MANY
Wait, hold on.
FOUND A RED DRESS SHIRT
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry"?
SORRY, SORRY
A WHITE DRESS SHIRT
I'm sorry.
NOT MIKE
KYUHYUN ENTERS THE RECEPTION
I'm sorry.
EXPRESS THEIR APOLOGIES
I'm sorry. Could he be hiding somewhere?
THEY'RE WEARING DRESS SHIRTS
HELLO
Are you Mike?
-No.
-I'm sorry.
A POLITE YOUNG MAN
WHO NEVER FORGETS HIS GRATITUDE
SU-GEUN VISITS THE SOUVENIR SHOP
Is there Mike?
-I'm sorry.
-"I'm sorry"?
Oh, Mike, where are you?
WONDERING IF HE'S DOING OKAY
No, I'm sorry.
DROWNING IN APOLOGIES
I don't think he's here.
Mike!
Oh, Mike!
WARM HUG AS A GREETING
HUGS
-What's your name?
-I'm Francis.
-Francis?
-I'm sorry.
HE'S NOT MIKE
IT WAS GREAT SEEING YOU THOUGH
THE IDIOTS ARE DESPERATELY LOOKING FOR HIM
WHERE IS MIKE?
IT'S ME
MIKE
40 YEARS OLD, SERVICE MANAGER
SMILEY FACE, BEAUTIFUL HEAD,
IN A DRESS SHIRT AND PANTS
WHERE IS HE?
IN THE BACK AREA OF THE RESTAURANT
ORGANIZING DISHES
"Nice to see you."
PREPARES HIS KOREAN LINE
Was it "I'm sorry"?
EVEN HELPS OUT HIS COLLEAGUE'S KOREAN LINE
LOOKING AT THE IDIOTS PASSING BY
WAITING ENDLESSLY
He's nowhere to be found.
JI-WON IS BACK AT FINDING MIKE AGAIN
OVER THERE
Restaurant? Oh, thank you!
Thank you, Owen!
FIGURED OUT MIKE'S WORKPLACE
Where is it though?
RUNNING TOWARD THE OUTSIDE
RECEPTION IS THE PLACE FOR ANSWERS
RESUMES RUNNING AFTER GETTING AN ANSWER
REACHES THE RESTAURANT WITH HELP
Mike?
I'm sorry.
WAS SO CLOSE TO WINNING
HE DISAPPEARED INTO THIN AIR
A MOMENT AGO…
HE LEFT AFTER GETTING HIS WORK DONE
ALMOST RAN INTO JI-WON
WHEN HE WAS RUSHING INTO THE RESTAURANT
HE LEFT THROUGH A DIFFERENT EXIT
AS JI-WON WALKED INTO THE RESTAURANT
MIKE IS ON HIS WAY TO THE LOUNGE BAR
CURRENTLY WORKING AT THE BAR
I'M SO BUSY
-Ji-won.
-I think he's hiding.
I can't find him anywhere.
I've been there.
SECRETLY ASKING FOR HELP
Over there?
SU-GEUN RUSHES OVER
She said somewhere over there.
JI-WON WAS LINGERING AROUND THE RESTAURANT
BOTH ARE VERY CLOSE TO MIKE
AT THAT VERY MOMENT
MIKE STEPS OUTSIDE
PASSES BY JI-WON
AN IDIOT WHO DOESN'T GET A CLUE
I can't find him anywhere.
Mike!
Jambo, Mike!
You can't just call anyone Mike.
I'm sorry.
APOLOGIZING ON BEHALF OF SU-GEUN
LIKE AN IDIOT
Mike!
SU-GEUN RUNS REGARDLESS
Are you Mike?
-Nice to see you.
-"Nice to see you"?
AFTER ALL THAT SEARCHING,
MIKE STANDS BEFORE HIM
SU-GEUN WINS
Hakuna matata
HERE YOU GO
THE 1ST PRIZE IS AWARDED TO SU-GEUN
FINALLY FREE FROM ALL THE APOLOGIES
SAVORING THE VICTORY
TODAY IS JUST ONE OF THOSE PERFECT DAYS
Oh, man, Mike.
IT'S A SHAME
AND THERE IS PUMBAA
CATCHING UP WITH THE SITUATION
Where was he?
REVEALING THE WINNER'S ROOM
AMAZED
The bed is…
XXL SIZE BED JUST FOR SU-GEUN
-The view is just…
-It is great.
FASCINATED
THE MAIN FEATURE OF WINNER'S ROOM
THE SAFARI VIEW
WHEN YOU RELAX ON THE BED
A GRASSLAND SCREEN STRETCHES OUT
IN FRONT OF YOU
You can just sit and enjoy the view.
MESMERIZED BY THE VIEW
I love the fact that there is a fan.
THE IDIOT LOVES THE FAN
AS MUCH AS THE VIEW
AMAZED
Su-geun.
Come look at this.
-The shower area is awesome.
-This is so cool.
-What is it?
-This is the place.
ENJOY A SHOWER IN THE HEART OF NATURE
You can relax while you poop.
Wow, what is this?
Your poop view.
It's a view for Pumbaa.
-Come visit my place.
-What?
-Leave your things.
-After I unpack…
-Can I use the bathroom first?
-Take a rest.
-Su-geun, record yourself in the bathroom.
-Okay.
REQUESTING A BATHROOM VLOG
He wants me to record it?
SOMEONE WHO CAN'T SAY NO
This is something…
Perhaps stepping outside
is a better option.
THEY ARRIVE AT THEIR ROOM
This is just as good.
-It's two individual beds.
-It's fine.
I like this room.
The flowing water sounds nice.
FOREST VIEW WITH WATER ASMR
The view is not bad.
-The sound of water is calming.
-Yes.
It's nice.
I'm satisfied.
PLEASED WITH THE SECOND LODGE
I'm going to swim.
Today…
I'm streaming from Kenya.
Let's enjoy a session
of upper-body exercises this afternoon.
SU-GEUN'S SAFARI WORKOUT SESSION
Starting with a Pumbaa exercise!
1. PUMBAA EXERCISE
This exercise targets
your back and chest muscles.
Stretch your back legs, bend your arms,
go straight down, and come back up.
AN EXERCISE INSPIRED BY PUMBAA
Get a body like this in just three months
with this workout.
GAIN MUSCLES LIKE PUMBAA WITH THIS ROUTINE
2. ELEPHANT EXERCISE
This is the most difficult one of all.
Oh, is it?
Let me demonstrate.
You lower yourself with your arms twisted.
It makes you work
the lower half of your body.
-Are you breathing okay?
-Yes, I mean…
OXYGEN-DEPRIVED WORKOUT
3. HIPPO EXERCISE
Shape our arms like a hippo's large mouth.
On one, you open your arms wide.
On two, squat and spread them wider.
One, two, three, and four.
MORE EFFECTIVE
IF THE ARMS ARE OPENED WIDER
-The hippo is moving in for a drink.
-One, two, three, and four.
One, two, three, and four.
Hey, Pumbaa. Come on!
You're already close.
DOOR-TO-DOOR SERVICE
Which one is Pumbaa?
EYE CONTACT
Damn it.
SCARED
-Were you intimidated?
-We made eye contact.
AFTER THE WORKOUT SESSION
THE IDIOTS ARE GATHERED UNDER A TREE
-Since you've had a good rest…
-Yes.
-…we'll begin the final game.
-Sounds great.
It looks like that person is in trouble.
-He's already surrounded.
-It's already too late.
Do you know the one-word term for it?
"Ganged up."
LAUGHS
-Hey, look at this one.
-What is it?
It's called hy…hylet? We saw it before.
Hy… It's hyrax.
-It's adorable.
-It's so cute.
THE CUTIE WE SAW EARLIER
-Dr. Eun, you know everything.
-I just saw it.
I asked a local about this animal.
-Come here, hyrax.
-It looks like it wants to join.
It's running away.
So, what was it again?
BACK TO THE MAIN POINT
Do you remember
why we first came to Kenya?
-Yes, the giraffe hotel.
-We came to see giraffes.
But since we haven't seen any giraffes,
we prepared a game.
It's the "Glistening-eyed Giraffe Game."
The name doesn't really interest me.
"The Glistening-eyed Giraffe Game"?
What could it be?
There is a legend
that makes its way across the Maasai Mara.
It is said that a unique giraffe
wanders across the Maasai Mara plains.
It's the glistening-eyed giraffe.
The Maasai say
that if you can find this giraffe,
you will gain a treasure
that sparkles like its glistening eyes.
However, not just anyone
can obtain the treasure.
Only by overcoming five great trials
can one meet the glistening-eyed giraffe.
Which idiot will discover the giraffe
and earn the gleaming treasure?
Legend says that if you find the giraffe,
-you will be rewarded with a diamond.
-Oh, really?
IT'S FICTION
If you visit all five animal houses
and complete their mission,
you will receive a hint
to find the glistening-eyed giraffe.
-That's…
-That must be Pumbaa's house.
I saw some holes.
THIS HOUSE BELONGS TO ANOTHER ANIMAL
HOUSES OF FIVE ANIMALS
5 MISSION LOCATIONS
SCATTERED THROUGHOUT THE LODGE
If you come in first,
you'll receive a diamond from the giraffe.
THE PERSON WHO MEETS THE GIRAFFE
WILL BE GIVEN A DIAMOND
THAT SHINES LIKE ITS GLISTENING EYES
HOWEVER
The two who fail to find it
will get to have a friendly chat
with another giraffe tomorrow.
TOMORROW
-Is this one?
-Kelly is all set for everything.
WHAT COULD POSSIBLY BE PREPARED?
I'm going to give out the first hint.
Take a look and find the first location.
GIVEN TO THE IDIOTS
ARE A MYSTERIOUS CODE AND A MAP
CODE: FOLLOW, FOLLOW, BUFFALO ME
A MYSTERIOUS CODE
LOUNGE (CURRENT LOCATION)
HOUSE NUMBER 27 MARKED WITH A STAR
You can start as soon as you are ready.
LET'S CHECK OUT HOUSE 27
-Are we going to the same place?
-Yes.
The first mission is… Why are you running?
This way to the pool…
These are all routes.
SU-GEUN GOES IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION
THE IDIOTS HAVE SPLIT INTO TWO PATHS
Is this the right place?
JI-WON AND KYUHYUN WALK THROUGH THE FOREST
I don't think this is it.
THEY REACH A DEAD END
-I think something will jump out.
-Is this it?
I guess this isn't it.
THE YOUNGER ONES WANDER LOST
GUIDED BY YEARS OF WISDOM,
THE ELDEST STRIDES FORWARD
Here it is. I found it
COULD THIS BE THE FIRST ANIMAL'S HOUSE?
Is this the place?
What's the code?
"Follow, follow, buffalo me."
Wrong code.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT HOUSE
I found one house though.
WHILE SU-GEUN VISITS THE WRONG HOUSE
KYUHYUN ESCAPES FROM THE DEAD END
Oh, damn it.
THE HOUSE FROM THE MAP IS JUST AHEAD
KYUHYUN IS ALMOST AT THE FIRST LOCATION
Okay, this is it.
SU-GEUN FINDS HIS WAY ONTO THE RIGHT PATH
There's a house over there.
We can't go?
There's no path there.
-We can go. We'll find a way.
-You're going that way?
PROACTIVE STYLE
I'm here.
WHO WILL BE THE FIRST CHALLENGER?
KYUHYUN ARRIVES FIRST
-What's the code?
-"Follow, follow, buffalo me."
JI-WON ARRIVES SECOND
I almost had it.
SU-GEUN ARRIVES LAST
The game is
"Part Buffalo's Hair Perfectly."
FIRST CHECKPOINT
BUFFALO'S HOUSE
PART BUFFALO'S HAIR PERFECTLY
JUST LIKE A BUFFALO
WITH A PERFECT HAIR PART
YOU HAVE TO OPEN THE BOOK IN THE MIDDLE
THE CORRECT PAGE IS HIGHLIGHTED
IF YOU FAIL,
READ THE PAGE YOU TURNED TO AND RETRY
Please choose a book of your choice.
SIGHS
FOUR BOOKS CHOSEN FOR INTELLECTUAL GROWTH
ON THE ORIGIN OF SPECIES
ROMEO AND JULIET
MINGXIN BAOJIAN
MYSTERY BOOK
I'll go with this unknown one.
KYUHYUN CHOOSES THE MYSTERIOUS COVER
-Exactly the middle page?
-Yes.
Three, two, one.
FAIL
Please move aside
and read the page on the right.
-Sorry, but this is in English.
-Yes, step aside.
ALICE'S ADVENTURES IN WONDERLAND
WRITTEN BY LEWIS CARROLL
THE STORY OF ALICE'S ADVENTURE
WE PREPARED AN ORIGINAL VERSION
FOR A REFINED TOUCH
UNEXPECTED PHONICS TIME
Chitsol?
Chushire?"
CHESHIRE CAT LOST ITS NAME
Please pick a book of your choice.
JI-WON'S TURN
A CAREFULLY CONSIDERED CHOICE
ROMEO AND JULIET
ONE OF SHAKESPEARE'S EARLY PLAYS
YOUNG LOVERS' TRAGEDY
A BOOK WITH MANY CHARACTERS,
WHICH REQUIRES GOOD ACTING SKILLS
Three, two, one.
FAIL
-Why did I fail?
-They say the answer is marked.
BATON PASS
SU-GEUN CHOOSES MINGXIN BAOJIAN
MINGXIN BAOJIAN
A CLASSIC WORK OF WISDOM AND MORALITY
CHINESE CHARACTERS PRESENT A CHALLENGE
Three, two, one.
AS EXPECTED, FAIL
MAASAI MARA LIBRARY IS OPEN
"We are undone, lady, we are undone!
Alack the day! He's…"
NURSE EUN
"To refuse learning
is like striving for the heavens.
Gaining wisdom through learning
is like standing atop
a lofty mountain to overlook all beneath.
By Zhuang Zhou."
RECITING FAMOUS QUOTES
A DEVOTED READER
"…I shall poison more
than the death-darting eye of cockatrice.
I am not…"
"What devil art thou…"
Wait, the nurse is the devil?
A SURPRISINGLY ENGAGING PLOT TWIST
"This torture should be roared
in dismal hell.
Hath Romeo slain himself?
Say thou but 'I.'"
"If he be slain, say 'I.'
Or if not, 'no.'"
HIP-HOP VERSION OF JULIET
"I saw the wound. I saw it with mine eyes.
God save the mark!"
"I swounded at the sight."
I've read it all.
-Would you like to switch books?
-No, I'll keep this one.
Three, two, one.
FAIL
It's the same page again! Damn it.
ENCORE
DURING JIWON'S ENCORE
-Would you like to switch books?
-Can I change it?
CHANGES TO ON THE ORIGIN OF SPECIES
ON THE ORIGIN OF SPECIES
CHARLES DARWIN
CORNERSTONE OF EVOLUTIONARY BIOLOGY
THE THICKNESS ITSELF IS A BARRIER
Three, two, one.
FAILED AGAIN
But it has a mark.
It's the back page. Please read it again.
DURING THIS BIOLOGY SESSION,
WE'LL LEARN ABOUT THE BEEHIVE STRUCTURE
"…the resulting structure
would probably have been
as perfect as the comb of the hive-bee.
Accordingly, I wrote to Professor Miller
of Cambridge, and this geometer…"
Can I pick another one?
KYUHYUN FINALLY FINISHES STUDYING ENGLISH
CHANGES TO MINGXIN BAOJIAN
Ready.
Three, two, one.
FAILED AGAIN
Hold on, there's only one sentence.
-Can I try again?
-No, you have to read the other page.
But it was the right page before.
THE WORDS ARE ON THE LEFT
RETRYING WITH THE SAME BOOK
Three, two, one.
It wasn't this side. Damn it.
3 CONSECUTIVE FAILURES
THE MAASAI LIBRARY
IS FULL OF EAGER READERS
What do I have to read this time?
"How should they,
when that wise men have no eyes?"
A NARRATIVE FULL OF INTENSIFIED EMOTIONS
AND
THE NON-FICTION ENTHUSIAST'S 3RD ATTEMPT
Three, two, one.
Oh, there it is.
PASS
-You pass!
-Nice, thank you.
You may go to the next house.
SU-GEUN PASSES
Here's the next mission location
and the code.
Which one is it?
CODE: DO NOT TWITCH, OSTRICH
CURRENT LOCATION
THE NEXT LOCATION IS A BIT FAR
Did you get it?
JEALOUS
How did he do it?
"Arise, one knocks.
Good Romeo, hide thyself--"
"…and teaches…"
RUNS AWAY AFTER TEASING THEM
DETENTION TIME FOR THE YOUNGER ONES
It's the one I found earlier.
Can I take the shortcut?
I can feel it's that house.
WILL HIS DEDUCTION BE CORRECT?
CURRENTLY 1ST PLACE: SU-GEUN
KYUHYUN FACES A CRITICAL SITUATION
There are Chinese characters.
It's all Chinese. Oh my…
NO LUCK WITH THE LANGUAGE ENCOUNTERS
Let's do this.
"As written in the Book of Rites…"
WENT WITH CHINESE,
NOT THE CHARACTER-BASED READING
FEATURING PAPAGO
"Seek out someone
who is necessarily generous, kind,
gentle, courteous,
prudent, and sparing in words,
and make that person
your child's teacher."
ALAS, A PHRASE BORROWED
FROM THE BOOK OF RITES
NO MORE ACTING AS THE NURSE BUT AS ROMEO
"Arise. One knocks, good Romeo.
Hide thyself.
Not I, unless
the breath of heartsick groans,
mist-like, infold me
from the search of eyes.
'Knocking.' Hark, how they knock!
Who's there?
Romeo, arise. Thou wilt be taken.
Stay awhile! Stand up.
'Knocking.' Run to my study!
By and by! God's will."
PEAK ACTING
"What simpleness is this! I come, I come!
'Knocking.' Who knocks so hard?
What's your will?
'Within.' Let me come in,
and you shall know my errand."
ACTED OUT WITH HIS UTMOST PASSION
-This page is worn out now, so--
-"…must not sit or eat together."
Did he pick a Chinese book?
FINALLY REALIZING THE SITUATION
"…must stay overnight outside the home."
Okay, done.
CHINESE STUDIES ARE FINALLY OVER
JI-WON RETRIES FIRST
Three, two, one.
AT LAST, IT'S THE MIDDLE PAGE
PASS
KYUHYUN GOES FOR A RETRY
-What's this?
-You've just opened it.
YOUNGER IDIOT CHOSE THE SAME BOOK
Three, two, one.
ALSO PASS
You did it? No way.
TOGETHER, THEY MOVE ON TO THE NEXT HOUSE
MEANWHILE, SU-GEUN
I think I'm lost.
TIME PASSING BY AS HE WANDERS LOST
Is it here? Wait… It's here.
I've been here before.
Oh, that's what the number was.
FINALLY ARRIVES
"Do not twitch, Ostrich."
This game is…
SECOND CHECKPOINT
OSTRICH'S HOUSE
OSTRICH-BEAK TYPING GAME
USE THE BEAK TO TYPE THE GIVEN WORD
THE TIME LIMIT IS 10 SECONDS
IF YOU FAIL, YOU MUST EAT A BOILED EGG
YOU CAN TRY AGAIN AFTER WHISTLING
TRANSFORMS INTO AN OSTRICH
-Does this actually work?
-Yes.
-Is it possible in ten seconds?
-Yes, ten seconds.
AT THE MOMENT
KYUHYUN IS ALREADY HERE
JI-WON ARRIVES AS WELL
HIS FIRST WORD IS
It's "mbuzi stew."
MBUZI STEW
WATCH OUT FOR SPACING
DIFFICULTY: 4 STARS
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
Set, go.
10-SECOND COUNTDOWN
OFF TO A GOOD START
MBU…
WRONG KEY
-Damn it.
-You messed up.
SU-GEUN FAILS
TIME TO EAT AN EGG
Do I eat this without salt?
UNFAMILIAR WITH A SODIUM-FREE DIET
FALLING
-Looks like you're tossing half away.
-No, I don't mess with food.
-It's whole.
-Sure.
IN ONE GO
KYUHYUN TRANSFORMS INTO AN OSTRICH
Enter the given word within ten seconds.
-In ten seconds?
-Yes.
KYUHYUN'S FIRST WORD
-"Lululemon."
LULULEMON
A MANAGEABLE WORD
DIFFICULTY: 3 STARS
That's easy. I think he can do it.
-I'm ready.
-Set, go
BEGINS TYPING
THE PECKING CONTINUES
I think your time is up.
SLIPS
Oh no.
KYUHYUN FAILS
Can anyone do this in ten seconds?
FINISH YOUR EGG PLEASE
NURSE EUN… NO, OSTRICH EUN'S TURN
What is this?
High difficulty.
MIX OF LOWERCASE AND UPPERCASE
-He's going to make it.
-Set, go.
PECKS
-What are you doing?
-Did I do it?
Nothing happened.
We need ten more seconds.
-Why is it not working?
-You are not pressing hard…
-You failed.
-Fail.
-Why?
-Time's up.
You entered two commas.
EGGS FOR EVERYONE
CHEWING
Gosh, I can't get it down.
I'm getting a lot of protein today.
BULK-UP DAY
Did anyone succeed?
I can manage four to five syllables.
You may go again.
-Show us.
-"Tuko Pamoja"?
THE IDIOTS' CATCHPHRASE
That actually seems possible.
Set, go.
THE GAME STARTS
-Oh, he did it.
-Is it "ko"?
-Come eat your egg.
-Yes, what are you doing over there?
-Oh no.
-Here is your egg.
FAIL
Since it's too difficult,
-I'll give you 15 seconds.
-Exactly, this is impossible.
THE TIME LIMIT IS 15 SECONDS
SU-GEUN'S TURN
-What is it?
-"Chommelier."
-It's only three syllables.
-Chommerlier.
Set, go. You have 15 seconds.
STARTING OFF QUICKLY THIS TIME
CHOMME…
Oh, the consonant…
SILENT MISSION
PASS
-I did it.
-That was great.
SU-GEUN PASSES
NEXT LOCATION HINT FOR THE WINNER
CODE: CATCH A RHINO, CATCH A COLD (COUGH)
RECEPTION
NEXT LOCATION IS CLOSE TO THE LOUNGE
-I think we have to go to our base camp.
-Okay.
IT MUST BE THE HOUSE THEY SAW EARLIER
"Catch a rhino, catch a cold."
COUGH
Maybe you need to catch
something on a horn.
WHAT COULD BE WAITING FOR THEM?
CURRENTLY 1ST PLACE: SU-GEUN
AT THE OSTRICH'S HOUSE
-Didn't you eat?
-I did.
ON THEIR THIRD EGGS
Let's feed these to the Pumbaas.
A PILE OF EMPTY EGGSHELLS
I bet they will love them.
THEY DON'T EAT EGGSHELLS
KYUHYUN'S 4TH ATTEMPT
PUMBAA
FIRST TWO-SYLLABLE WORD
HIS HEART IS POUNDING
What's going on?
It's nothing.
-Ready?
-Wait, I'm not ready yet.
CAN'T HIDE HIS SMILE
Ready, set, go.
BEGINS TYPING
Wait!
Oh, no!
DESPITE ALL THE DISTRACTIONS
PUMBAA
KYUHYUN PASSES
-How long did he take?
-He took 13 seconds.
Which way do I go?
I have to go back to the reception.
MEANWHILE, SU-GEUN
The code?
-What's the code?
-"Catch a rhino, catch a cold. Cough."
This one's going to be tough.
-The game is "Cone, Cone, Rhino Cone."
-Okay.
THIRD CHECKPOINT
RHINO'S HOUSE
CONE, CONE, RHINO CONE
SPIN AROUND FIVE TIMES WITH THE CONE ON
FIND A SHOE AND PUT IT ON
THE FOOT MUST TOUCH THE SOLE
This is absurd.
40 EYELETS STAND IN YOUR WAY
I can't see a thing.
ONLY THE COLORS ARE DISTINGUISHABLE
THEREFORE, NOTHING IS VISIBLE
This is bad. I can't see anything.
-Should I start?
-"Catch a rhino?"
-"Catch a cold."
-Is this the line?
ARRIVES IN THE MIDDLE OF THE COMPLAINTS
One, two…
THE OLDER IDIOT STARTS
…three, four, five.
A RHINO GONE WILD FROM STRESS
WAIT
WHAT?
HE STAGGERS AHEAD WITH A DYING SCREAM
RUNS AWAY
-Can I start?
-Yes.
RHINO CHO STARTS THE CHALLENGE
EXPLORING THE GRASS LIKE PUMBAA
Four…
FOUND THE SHOE
…five.
THIS ONE HAS JUST STARTED WALKING
Oh, here it is.
TOSSES ASIDE
It's here, Kyuhyun.
INSTINCTIVE SABOTAGE
AT THE OSTRICH'S HOUSE
Oh, not this again, damn it.
CHATGPT AGAIN
I don't even use this thing.
Set, go.
LET THE GAME CONTINUE
MANAGING TO TYPE THE LETTERS THIS TIME
THE STAFF WATCHES OVER HIM
Please check the capitalization.
Don't say that. Why would you be so anal?
CHOKED UP
Do you really have to go that far?
I feel like throwing up.
There's a pungent smell rising
from my stomach.
FED UP WITH THE MONO DIET
Even the water tastes weird.
At least give me some soda.
Never drink lukewarm water
with boiled eggs.
It's the worst combination.
TAKES A BITE
My mouth is completely dry.
A TOUGH BATTLE WITH EGGS
ENDURES THE PAIN FOR ANOTHER TRY
I think this is the Lulu one.
FINALLY, AN EASY WORD
Set, go.
BEGINS TYPING WITH DETERMINATION
NOTICEABLY FASTER PACE
LULU…
I can't see very well.
LULULEMON
PASS
SLICE OF LIFE OF A TYPING OSTRICH
I can actually do it really well.
-I won't forget what you did to me.
-Take the hint.
What's the hint?
FINALLY OUT OF THE OSTRICH'S HOUSE
RUNNING OFF
Oh, the chickens are growing!
They're growing bigger in my stomach!
READY TO LAY EGGS
OUT OF BREATH
I'm too old to run now.
AN EMOTIONAL DAY FOR A 47-YEAR-OLD
How did it get tighter?
I don't get how it ended up so tight.
ALSO STRUGGLING
It's faster if you untie it first.
Damn it.
Untie it first?
They snapped off the zipper pull.
JUST TO PREVENT ANY SNEAKY MOVES
They truly are something.
Just untie them all?
TAKING THE DIRECT APPROACH
AFTER GIVING UP SHORTCUTS
JI-WON IS FINALLY HERE
"Catch a rhino, catch a cold. Cough."
AT THE MOMENT
-I put them on.
-Okay, pass.
KYUHYUN PASSES
CURRENT RANKING
1ST, 2ND, 3RD
SU-GEUN HAS BEEN OVERTAKEN
EXHALES
You can grab the hint.
CODE: I'M THE KING OF THE JUNGLE! ROAR
CURRENT LOCATION
THE NEXT LOCATION IS VERY CLOSE
I believe it's over there.
KYUHYUN FIGURED IT OUT IN ONE GO
"I'm the king of the jungle. Roar."
Welcome to the lion's room.
The game is "Roar, Buy a Souvenir."
FOURTH CHECKPOINT
LION'S HOUSE
ROAR, BUY A SOUVENIR
CHECK OUT THE 4 SOUVENIRS
FIND THE PRICE OF EACH WITHIN 2 MINUTES
CALCULATE THE TOTAL IN YOUR HEAD
AND GET IT CORRECT
IF YOU FAIL,
WAIT 1 MINUTE BEFORE TRYING AGAIN
The items you need to find are…
-What are these?
-You can find everything in here.
KYUHYUN'S COMBO
1. BROWN LEATHER BAG
2. LEOPARD-PRINT SHIRT
3. RED BRACELET
4. CHEETAH-SHAPED KNIFE
ITEMS ARE SCATTERED THROUGHOUT THE STORE
You have two minutes. Ready, set, go.
THE GAME STARTS
Since Kyuhyun is really good at math…
He used to be in math competitions.
HOWEVER…
SIMILAR LOOKING HATS
SIMILAR LOOKING BELTS
SIMILAR LOOKING ACCESSORIES
SIMILAR LOOKING FIGURES
SIMILAR LOOKING SCULPTURES
A COLLECTION OF SOUVENIRS
THAT ARE ALIKE YET SUBTLY DIFFERENT
AND A LITTLE LAMB LOST INSIDE
You have 30 seconds remaining.
No way, where are they?
90 SECONDS PASSED BY MEANINGLESSLY
Oh, I found one.
RUMMAGING THROUGH THE CLOTHING RACK
LEOPARD-PRINT SHIRT, $65
The bag…
BROWN BAG, $199
CHEETAH-SHAPED KNIFE, $89
Where is the bracelet?
ONLY THE BRACELET IS LEFT TO FIND
DOUBLE-CHECKS THE ITEM
-Is there a case?
-What?
Oh, it's here. I can't believe it.
FOUND IT WITH 15 SECONDS TO SPARE
RED BRACELET, $10
RELYING ON MENTAL CALCULATION
Ten seconds remaining.
Four, three, two, one.
RETREATS
FAIL
AT RHINO'S HOUSE
I did it.
SU-GEUN PASSES
I can't take this anymore.
ENERGY DRAINED THROUGH ALL THE EYELETS
RHINO EUN BEGINS TO SPIN
Oh my.
Isn't that a Pumbaa?
YOUNGER IDIOT ON THE FLOOR
OLDER IDIOT GOES HIS WAY
That shoe drove me crazy.
LOST FOR SOME REASON
"I'm the king…" Mission…
"I'm the king of the jungle. Roar."
ROARING AT MIKE FOR NO REASON
I'm sorry.
This is insane.
Why are they acting
like they're part of the mission?
"I'm the king…"
"I'm the king of the jungle. Roar."
I'M SORRY…
Ten seconds remaining.
Oh, it's him.
SU-GEUN FINALLY JOINS
"I'm the king of the jungle. Roar."
I've checked everywhere.
Why couldn't I think of this place?
The items you need to find are…
-We can't use our phone, right?
-Of course not, are you kidding?
AWKWARD
SU-GEUN'S COMBO
1. BROWN HAT
2. MAASAI PLATE
3. WILDLIFE GUIDEBOOK
4. ELEPHANT SCULPTURE
Ready, set, go.
STARTS THE SEARCH
How can I do this in two minutes?
Oh, it's here.
You're clever, Kyuhyun.
JI-WON, KYUHYUN
1 MINUTE'S UP
HEADS STRAIGHT TO GIVE HIS ANSWER
Is the time up?
-Did you perhaps finish the calculations?
-Of course.
What's your answer?
-It's 363 dollars.
-I can't find the hat.
-You said…
-It's 363 dollars.
Correct.
KYUHYUN PASSES
I'll wait for you, Su-geun.
KYUHYUN STAYS IN 1ST PLACE
Should I take it easy?
I don't think he'll make it.
Oh, I can't see. I should've worn glasses.
KYUHYUN WAS RIGHT ON POINT
Is this it? I don't think it is.
Is the color different?
THIS IS THE ONE
BROWN HAT, $65
Oh, I found it.
MAASAI PLATE, $9
FOUND THE GUIDEBOOK AS WELL
WILDLIFE GUIDEBOOK, $65
BROWN HAT, GUIDEBOOK, MAASAI PLATE
ONLY THE ELEPHANT SCULPTURE IS LEFT
Come on.
THE ELEPHANT IS NOWHERE TO BE SEEN
But the elephant is big.
This is driving me crazy.
Oh, it's here.
FINALLY FOUND THE ELEPHANT SCULPTURE
I think this is the one.
Or is this the one?
10 OTHER SCULPTURES IN DIFFERENT SIZES
Seems like the prices vary.
SU-GEUN PICKS THE 15-DOLLAR SCULPTURE
What's the answer?
Is it 185 dollars?
-Do you mean to say 185 dollars?
-Yes.
-Wrong!
-How did I end up with that number?
CAN'T GET HIS ADDITION RIGHT
Wait, so it's not 185 dollars?
MUST WAIT FOR 1 MINUTE
I forgot the original price.
-Did Ji-won go home?
-His task is really difficult.
AT RHINO'S HOUSE
JI-WON FINALLY FOUND THE SHOES
Gosh, I want to give up.
Seriously.
SUCH A LONG DAY FOR JI-WON
Which kind of idiot brings
these shoes to Kenya, huh?
Has he lost his mind?
UNTYING THE SHOELACES IN ANGER
I bet he's the type of person who has
to wake up at 4 a.m. to get ready on time.
SHOVING HIS FEET IN
WITHOUT UNTYING THE LACES
RAMPAGE
SAVE ME
Are you sure these are men's shoes?
AFTER MUCH HARD WORK
-I did it.
-You passed.
SIGHS
I'm so exhausted.
A LITTLE LATER
I failed due to my poor memory.
ENTERS WITH A DETERMINED LOOK
You've arrived.
You look very exhausted.
"I didn't realize
that I was actually Pumbaa."
That won't work.
It's about time I won.
KYUHYUN HEADS TO THE LAST ANIMAL HOUSE
RECEPTION
LOUNGE
CODE: DON'T BE A HIPPO-CRITE
WHICH CHALLENGE AWAITS THE IDIOTS?
What's the code?
"Don't be a hippo-crite."
-The game is "Water-drinking Hippo."
-"Water-drinking Hippo?"
You'll work with the giraffe brothers here
to solve a problem together.
THE GIRAFFE BROTHERS ARE BACK
FIFTH CHECKPOINT
HIPPO'S HOUSE
THE WATER-DRINKING HIPPO GAME
BALANCE A WATER-FILLED BASIN
WITH THE GIRAFFES
EACH HAS TO TAKE TURNS
IN TAKING OFF THEIR SOCKS
THEN PUT THEM BACK ON TO SUCCEED
IF THE WATER SPILLS, HE FAILS
How do we do this?
Here comes the water basin.
Oh my goodness.
Hold on.
POSITIONING THE BASIN
Who wants to go first?
Should I go first? Can you handle it?
KYUHYUN GOES FIRST
Okay.
CAREFULLY LIFTS HIS LEFT FOOT
NERVOUS
HE SUCCESSFULLY TAKES ONE OFF
NOW HE MUST REMOVE THE RIGHT SOCK
Oh my gosh.
THE WATER IS TILTING TO ONE SIDE
Hold on.
We can do this.
KYUHYUN FINISHES HIS TURN
Who wants to go next?
-I'll do it.
-Sure.
THE BIGGER GIRAFFE GOES NEXT
STRIPS
Hold on.
Are you done already?
HOWEVER
SLOWLY LOSING STRENGTH IN THEIR LEGS
DRIPS
I'm on my right foot.
I think we need to pull this up.
SPILLS
LOSING WATER LITTLE BY LITTLE
My gosh, pull it up from that side.
Wait a minute.
Can we adjust our positions?
Try holding it up.
My feet are stiff.
-Come back.
-It's like his feet are gone.
WHILE KYUHYUN IS LEADING
THE GIRAFFE BROTHERS
AT LION'S HOUSE
You'll be playing "Roar, Buy a Souvenir."
Find the following items.
JI-WON'S PACKAGE
1. TRIVET
2. BOTTLE OPENER
3. NECKLACE
4. STUFFED ELEPHANT
Your time starts now.
STARTS HIS SEARCH
My extra minute is over.
Come in and continue playing.
RUNS TO CHECK THE ELEPHANT
PICKS THE ELEPHANT WITH CAUTION
SU-GEUN PICKS
THE 11-DOLAR ELEPHANT THIS TIME
-Here.
-Great choice.
The math works out the same as earlier.
It's 150 dollars.
-That's different from before.
-Yes.
-Is your answer 150 dollars?
-Correct!
-Thank you!
I guess I miscalculated earlier.
My answer is 150 dollars.
Wrong, you have different items.
Go back and do the math.
-Oh, we have different items?
-That's right.
I knew it.
MEANWHILE, SU-GEUN RECEIVES HIS CLUE
This is too far.
I feel like number eight is my room.
HEADING TO HIS ROOM
Let's go.
CURRENT RANKING:
1ST KYUHYUN, 2ND SU-GEUN, 3RD JI-WON
Hold on. That's 40-something.
This is 38, and that's 4 dollars,
so that would be 42 dollars.
I think this is the one.
STUFFED ELEPHANT, $40
This is it.
TRIVET, $21
You have 30 seconds left.
JI-WON FOUND ALL HIS ITEMS
WITH 30 SECONDS REMAINING
JI-WON'S EXPECTED ANSWER
-I have an answer.
-Go ahead.
-It's 103 dollars.
-Correct.
-All right.
-That was quick.
This is your next destination.
-"Don't be a hippo…"
-Run, Ji-won!
Number eight?
JI-WON STARTS RACING
Number eight
is somewhere near Su-geun's room.
WILL HE CATCH UP?
All right.
AT HIPPO'S HOUSE
Start with your right foot.
IT'S DOWN TO KYUHYUN AND THE BIG GIRAFFE
WHO NEED TO WEAR IT BACK
STRUGGLING
THE MISSION SEEMS
A BIT CHALLENGING FOR HIM
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Don't rush it. Let's slow down.
Take your time.
SUPER CHARISMATIC
Okay, go.
FOLLOWING THE LEADER'S WORDS
We're almost there.
KYUHYUN IS THE ONLY ONE LEFT
TREMBLING
We can do it. We're almost there.
I just have one foot left.
Just hang in there.
Can you do that for me?
Okay!
HE WEARS IT SWIFTLY
-Pass!
-We did it!
KYUHYUN PASSES
Thank you. Great job, guys.
SORE ALL OVER
-Let's do a celebration.
-Which one?
ALLIANCE FORGED THROUGH A WATER BASIN
KYUHYUN OVERCAME ALL FIVE CHALLENGES
-Next.
-This is your last hint.
THE LAST STOP TO FIND
THE GLISTENING-EYED GIRAFFE
AN UNKNOWN, MYSTERIOUS WORD
What's a kuogolea?
Am I supposed to find this on my own?
WHAT DOES KUOGOLEA MEAN?
WHILE KYUHYUN IS FIGURING OUT
THE MYSTERIOUS WORD
"Don't be a hippo-crite."
SU-GEUN ARRIVES JUST IN TIME
This is impossible, Su-geun.
LYING OUT OF HABIT
I don't care.
-The game is "Water-drinking Hippo."
-Okay.
This is a game you have to solve
with the giraffe brothers here.
THEY GO TO THEIR POSITIONS LIKE A ROUTINE
I've got good control over my feet.
Let's do it. I'm good at this.
STARTS OUT CONFIDENTLY
I wore my socks too tightly.
HERE COMES THE WATER BASIN
That much water?
Darn it.
-It's really hard.
-Are you ready?
Maintain your balance.
FUN BECAUSE IT'S NOT HIS BUSINESS ANYMORE
How do I take these off?
-With your hands.
-I can use my hands?
TAKES BOTH FEET OFF THE BASIN
You have to keep one foot attached.
EXHAUSTED
I need to leave now.
KYUHYUN LEAVES IN A HURRY
Hold on.
Go ahead. Let your foot go.
Why would you take your feet off?
NOT IN THEIR RIGHT MINDS
DUE TO EXHAUSTION
I think he's doing this on purpose.
No, put your left foot attached.
Did Kyuhyun make it?
He cleared this and left?
Wait, Kyuhyun actually cleared this?
The giraffes must be too tired to do it.
I bet they're exhausted
after doing it for three minutes with me.
"Kuogolea."
DOESN'T HAVE A CLUE
What is kuogolea?
Is it 9552?
-That was impressive, wasn't it?
-Sure.
But where is it?
I'm sure we'll end up
back to where we started, right?
FOLLOWING HIS GUT FEELING
BACK TO THE LOUNGE WHERE THEY STARTED
THEY'RE NOW TRYING TO PUT THEM BACK ON
A UNIQUE TACTIC OF STRUGGLING ALONE
This is too exhausting for me.
GIRAFFES ARE DONE WITH THEIR SOCKS
Hold the basin steadily.
I did a good job, didn't I?
ONLY SU-GEUN'S SOCKS ARE REMAINING
I'm almost done. This isn't impossible.
-Look.
-Pass.
THEIR LEGS GIVE OUT THE MOMENT THEY FINISH
CLATTER
-Oh my goodness.
-I'm so sorry.
-You're such a piece of trash.
-So sorry.
I didn't mean it.
SU-GEUN GETS HIS LAST CLUE
What's this?
What could this mean?
-Help me out, Ji-won.
-What?
-If you clear this round for me--
-Forget it, I'm leaving.
REJECTS THE DEAL WITHOUT MERCY
KYUHYUN IS BACK AT THE STARTING POINT
Look, it's Super Junior.
Kuogolea!
-Aren't you a member of Super Junior?
-I am.
Kuogolea!
What's that?
I GUESS THIS ISN'T THE SPOT
What's kuogolea, then?
Kuogolee. Kugolia?
What is this?
SU-GEUN HAS NO CLUE EITHER
Should I translate this to Korean?
I think kuogolea means something
in the local language.
Excuse me.
ASKING THE STAFF FOR HELP
Here, kuogolea.
No way. I have to go to the swimming pool.
WE ASKED A LOCAL
TO READ THE MYSTERIOUS WORD
LUCY
61 YEARS IN KENYA
Kuogolea, the Swahili word for swimming.
WHICH MEANS
A BEAUTIFUL POOL
OVERLOOKING THE SAFARI
A STRANGE OBJECT IN THE MIDST OF IT
FLOATING ALL ALONE
IS THE GLISTENING-EYED GIRAFFE
HOWEVER
FLOATING
Kuogolea?
THE CURRENT FIRST PLACE HAS NO CLUE
Kuogolea!
YELLING KUOGOLEA ENDLESSLY
What does it mean?
Kuogolea!
RIGHT UNDER KYUHYUN'S NOSE
What is it?
Kuogolea?
PLEASE SAVE ME
THE GLISTENING-EYED GIRAFFE
IS GETTING ALL BLOATED
WHILE THE GIRAFFE IS ASKING FOR HELP
HE TAKES A QUICK TURN TOWARD THE GIRAFFE
DISCOVERS THE GIRAFFE
That's the one, right?
We're here to look for the giraffe.
GETTING READY TO GO UNDERWATER
RIGHT AT THAT MOMENT
I think I'll go to the swimming pool.
I've got a feeling.
SU-GEUN ARRIVES AT THE POOL AS WELL
I'll go straight ahead.
SU-GEUN
WHO WILL GET THE GIRAFFE IN THE END?
My gosh!
TAKING ONE STEP CLOSER
TO THE GIRAFFE WITH A CRY
IT'S TOO DEEP FOR KYUHYUN
TO GRAB THE GIRAFFE
SU-GEUN IS RIGHT BEHIND HIM
What are you doing?
I GOT IT!
THE GLISTENING-EYED GIRAFFE
HAS COME OUT TO THE WORLD
SU-GEUN MISSED IT BY A HAIR
Kuogolea!
KYUHYUN IS THE FINAL WINNER
The race has ended.
What a bummer.
KYUHYUN WINS THE DIAMOND
EXCLAIMS
I don't think we ever asked you
to make that pose.
DOING A DANCE OF JOY
You're a full-on entertainer now.
The funny thing is that Ji-won
is still doing his game.
AT HIPPO'S HOUSE
EXCLAIMS
GASPS
SPILLS
You did that on purpose.
WRONGFULLY ACCUSED
I felt how you were exerting
too much force!
If I'm going to lose anyway,
I'd rather be eliminated now.
GLOOMY AT THE THOUGHT
OF DOING MANUAL LABOR
Is this even necessary?
Wouldn't it be better to surrender now?
What do you think?
The race has ended.
It's over?
Why did we do this?
You should've eliminated me sooner.
I got wet for nothing.
BUT IT WAS FUN, WASN'T IT?
GATHER AT THE POOL
-We need to give Kyuhyun his prize.
-Right.
Here's the prize we promised.
This is a real diamond. Congratulations.
-Oh my gosh.
-Congrats.
0.5-CARAT NATURAL DIAMOND
This is amazing.
I'll keep this as a family heirloom.
-Congratulations on your win, Kyuhyun.
-Thank you.
You won because you kissed
the glistening-eyed giraffe.
You randomly added the word "kissed."
SUDDENLY FEELING UNEASY
We'll be kissing
a different kind of giraffe tomorrow.
-Are we really kissing them?
-Yes.
-Let me show you a photo.
-Did you take it yourself?
-This is what you'll do.
-What is going on?
THE GIRAFFE IS BOLDER THAN WE THOUGHT
It's practically eating his face up.
This is unexpected.
I'd still do it
if this were the only way to kiss one.
Do we wait for the kiss?
-We'll stay still with your eyes closed.
-We just have to stay still.
THEIR LAST DAY ENDS WITH EXCITEMENT
THE NEXT DAY
HE PUTS ON LIP BALM
AS HE GETS OUT OF THE CAR
We're about to meet them at last.
We're finally achieving our purpose
on our last day.
It's about time.
Let me remind you.
The giraffes here
work double shifts at the giraffe hotel.
They work at the hotel as well.
-We could've met them there, then.
-That's right.
THEIR LAST STOP
THE GIRAFFES HAVE MOVED
FROM THE GIRAFFE HOTEL
WHICH WAS THE IDIOTS' ORIGINAL DESTINATION
WHERE THEY PROTECT
AND CARE FOR THE ENDANGERED
ROTHSCHILD'S GIRAFFES
THE SITE OFFERS GIRAFFE-FEEDING ACTIVITIES
AND VARIOUS OTHER EXPERIENCES
WITH THE GIRAFFES
COME AND HAVE FUN WITH THE GIRAFFES
-Is that real? Wait, it's real.
-It is.
-Really?
-I thought it was a statue.
WELCOMING THE GUESTS FROM THE ENTRANCE
-It looks like a statue.
-It's pretty.
-It's pretty!
-Oh, it's right in front of us.
We need to get closer.
Look at its baby. It's adorable.
THIS ONE IS ONLY 15 DAYS OLD
How could such an animal exist on Earth?
It's coming after us
because it knows we have food.
BABY GIRAFFE WITHOUT HORNS
Don't those giraffes look a bit older?
NEWBORN GIRAFFES ARE RELEASED
AFTER SOME TIME IN THE SHELTER
KELLY, 24-YEAR-OLD FEMALE
TALL AND A LITTLE VICIOUS
AN INTIMATE MOMENT
WITH THE IDIOTS COMING SOON
AN ELDERLY GIRAFFE
WHO HAS WEATHERED TURMOILS
-She's a bit old.
-That's very old.
TIME FOR THEIR PENALTY
-Kelly is all set for everything.
-With Kelly.
Su-geun?
COME ON NOW
-Are you ready?
-I'll go first.
There's no way Ji-won will go first.
-How should I do it?
-I don't think it'll come near.
Put the treat here?
NERVOUS WITH EXCITEMENT
-Do I place it here?
-Move slowly.
Kelly.
CHOKING UP
-What does it feel like?
-How was it?
It was okay, but her tongue is so coarse.
That's what they evolved into.
-Because of acacia trees.
-Oh, right. They eat acacia trees.
-It felt very coarse.
-Try it one more time.
KELLY NEEDS TO MOISTURIZE HER LIPS
Ji-won is a scaredy-cat.
He looks worried.
JI-WON FEELS SMALL IN FRONT OF KELLY
EYES SHUT
Gosh.
LEAVES WITH A SHARP YELL
-You should've stayed longer.
-I did.
-I'll try longer. Hi, Kelly.
-Hey, Su-geun.
LICKING
That was impressive.
THE BEST LOVE STORY EVER
THE AFTERMATH OF THEIR LOVE
I did great, didn't I?
Kyuhyun wants to give it a try.
-Go ahead.
-This is your only chance.
-I feel like she doesn't like me.
-No, she likes you.
Give her one as a sample first
and move slowly.
-Hi, Kelly.
-Kelly.
CAREFULLY APPROACHING HER
Why are you trembling?
-Not too bad, right?
-Yes.
-It was okay.
-Not too bad.
-We didn't get saliva all over our faces.
-No, she didn't.
Thank you, Kelly,
for taking the video with us.
They're unbelievably beautiful.
THANKING HER
FOR THE ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME EXPERIENCE
-She's got beautiful eyes.
-Look, her eyes are adorable.
I loved it.
HAVE A SAFE TRIP
TAKING PHOTOS AFTER THE KISS
EDDY
A GENTLE 8-YEAR-OLD MALE
No way.
-He's insanely tall.
-Eddy.
You should smile.
TENSED UP
CHUCKLES
Eddy.
Oh, he almost ate my hand.
GIGGLES
THREE DIFFERENT PHASES
-Should I try it?
-Go ahead, I'll take your photo.
THE YOUNGEST IDIOT GOES FOR IT
Did you feel it?
GASPS
Take a look at this.
CHUCKLES
-That makes him look like a horse.
-It looks like a horse.
This is fun.
EDDY STILL FEELS QUITE DISTANT
I kissed a giraffe.
Four of us here did it.
AGREEING SHEEPISHLY
-Hey, there's more over there.
-There are ten of them in total.
SIGHS
I've got no regrets
now that I've seen all kinds of animals.
Humans are weak.
GETTING SENTIMENTAL
TOWARD THE END OF THEIR TRIP
Let's try laughing. Three, two, one.
MEMORIES WITH OLD FRIENDS
IN A FARAWAY LAND
Are you done yet?
We're done!
-Thank you.
-Good job, guys.
THE END FOR REAL!
Subtitle translation by: Grace Lee